[English subtitles are available]
[الترجمة الإنجليزية متوفرة]
[The Silence of the Monster]
[صمت الوحش]
[Episode 34]
[الحلقة 34]
[Just because I don't say it doesn't mean I don't care]
[فقط لأنني لا أقول ذلك لا يعني أنني لا أهتم]
I know
أنا أعرف
you won't be on the same boat with me.
لن تكون معي على نفس القارب.
Fine.
بخير.
I'll let you
سأدعك
go to hell with me.
اذهب الى الجحيم معي.
Mr. Jin.
السيد جين.
Boss is here.
بوس هنا.
I'll go there later.
سأذهب هناك لاحقًا.
Come out.
يخرج.
Boss.
رئيس.
You want to see me?
انت تريد ان تراني؟
During my absence,
أثناء غيابي،
you had a lot of fun.
كان لديك الكثير من المرح.
What fun did I have?
ما هي المتعة التي استمتعت بها؟
For the sake of your relationship
من أجل علاقتكما
with my sister,
مع أختي،
I took you into this business.
لقد أخذتك إلى هذا العمل.
But I didn't ask you
لكني لم أسألك
to intefere with my business.
للتدخل في عملي.
Xiuyi, let me explain.
Xiuyi ، اسمحوا لي أن أشرح.
I just
أنا فقط
wanted to make more money for you.
أردت أن تكسب المزيد من المال من أجلك.
I...
أنا...
You bought works from Qianhe Gallery
اشتريت أعمالًا من معرض Qianhe
and sold faked ones
وبيع المنتجات المزيفة
at twice the price.
بضعف السعر.
Jin, tell me.
جين ، أخبرني.
That's not all, right?
هذا ليس كل شيء ، أليس كذلك؟
But Xiuyi,
لكن Xiuyi ،
I have no selfish motive.
ليس لدي دافع أناني.
I promise you.
أعدك.
I swear.
أقسم.
So,
وبالتالي،
you made such a situation for me,
لقد صنعت مثل هذا الموقف من أجلي ،
such a mess,
يا لها من فوضى،
right?
الصحيح؟
No.
لا.
I...
أنا...
I'll clean up
سوف أنظف
this mess right away.
هذه الفوضى على الفور.
I'll clean it up for you.
سأقوم بتنظيفه من أجلك.
I won't cause you any trouble, okay?
لن تسبب لك أي مشكلة ، حسنًا؟
Jin.
جين.
This mess
هذه الفوضى
is good.
جيد.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Yes.
نعم.
[If you call the police, he'll die.]
[إذا اتصلت بالشرطة ، فسوف يموت.]
Mr. He.
السيد.  هو.
You're here.
أنت هنا.
Where is Robin?
أين روبن؟
Calm down, Mr. He.
اهدأ ، سيد هو.
Your friend
صديقك
is taken good care of by Mr. Jin.
يتم الاعتناء به من قبل السيد جين.
Mr. He,
السيد.  هو،
since you are here,
بما أنك هنا
let's make a deal.
لنعقد صفقة.
Cut the crap.
قطع الفضلات.
Where's Robin?
أين روبن؟
You want to save your friend?
تريد حفظ صديقك؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
But I'm a businessman.
لكن أنا رجل أعمال.
What do businessmen care about the most?
ما الذي يهتم به رجال الأعمال أكثر؟
Profits.
أرباح.
Yes.
نعم.
You don't care about that.
أنت لا تهتم بذلك.
What do you care about?
ماذا يهمك؟
Justice.
عدالة.
Friends.
أصدقاء.
Affection.
عاطِفَة.
Don't you think these
لا تعتقد هذه
are your weaknesses?
هي نقاط ضعفك؟
Where is Robin?
أين روبن؟
You want to find him.
تريد أن تجده.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Two prerequisites.
متطلبان أساسيان.
First,
أولاً،
buy him back with money.
شرائه بالمال.
-Second... -I have no money.
ثانيا .. ليس لدي مال.
You didn't listen to my second prerequisite.
أنت لم تستمع إلى شرطي الثاني.
I don't join hands with bad guys.
أنا لا أتكاتف مع الأشرار.
Bad guy?
شاب سيء؟
Tell me what's good
قل لي ما هو جيد
and what's bad.
وما هو سيء.
Why do you think the police need your help?
لماذا تعتقد أن الشرطة بحاجة إلى مساعدتك؟
They're just watching you
إنهم يشاهدونك فقط
in another way.
بطريقة أخرى.
But you
لكنك
are willing to work for them.
هم على استعداد للعمل معهم.
Why don't you join me,
لماذا لا تنضم الي
join us?
انضم إلينا؟
I can help you
أستطيع مساعدتك
and your friends
وأصدقائك
make a lot of money.
يعمل الكثير من المال.
This world is dirty.
هذا العالم قذر.
The survival of the fittest
والبقاء للأصلح
is always the rule.
هو دائما القاعدة.
Money
نقود
is the most important.
الأكثر أهمية.
So is desire.
هكذا هي الرغبة.
The cooperation between the strongest
التعاون بين الأقوى
is the only way out.
هو السبيل الوحيد للخروج.
Some people have a lot of money
بعض الناس لديهم الكثير من المال
but forget the password.
لكن نسيت كلمة المرور.
Some people can pick many locks
يمكن لبعض الأشخاص اختيار العديد من الأقفال
but they don't have much money.
لكن ليس لديهم الكثير من المال.
Move a few fingers
حرك بضعة أصابع
and you can have countless money.
ويمكن أن يكون لديك أموال لا حصر لها.
What are you still thinking about?
ما الذي ما زلت تفكر فيه؟
I don't believe you haven't been moved.
لا أصدق أنك لم تتحرك.
I don't have time
ليس لدي وقت
to talk about your financial views and worldview.
للتحدث عن آرائك المالية ونظرتك للعالم.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Where is Robin?
أين روبن؟
Are you talking about brotherhood?
هل تتحدث عن الاخوة؟
You remind me of
أنت تذكرني بـ
a good friend of mine.
صديق جيد لي.
A very good friend.
صديق جيد جدا.
He committed suicide.
انتحر.
Do you know why?
هل تعرف لماذا؟
That's your business.
هذا هو عملك.
It has nothing to do with me.
لا يمتلك شيئا ليفعله معي.
Your master
سيدك
doesn't want you to be happy.
لا تريد أن تكون سعيدا.
What should you do?
ماذا عليك ان تفعل؟
It's all
كل شئ
his idea
فكرته
to ask your best friend
لتسأل أفضل صديق لك
to come here.
لتأتي إلى هنا.
I suddenly found it interesting.
فجأة وجدت أنها مثيرة للاهتمام.
I didn't want to get involved,
لم أرغب في المشاركة ،
but I changed my mind.
لكني غيرت رأيي.
Gu Nan
قو نان
is so stupid
هذا غبي جدا
and worthless.
ولا قيمة لها.
You're so interesting.
أنت ممتع جدا.
I should talk to you.
يجب أن أتحدث معك.
We are not the same kind.
نحن لسنا من نفس النوع.
There's nothing to talk about.
لا يوجد شيء للحديث عنه.
Not the same kind.
ليس من نفس النوع.
He is the illegitimate child.
هو الولد غير الشرعي.
He's an illegitimate child.
إنه طفل غير شرعي.
Just because I'm not the same kind,
فقط لأنني لست من نفس النوع ،
so I don't have any chance?
لذلك ليس لدي أي فرصة؟
So I don't have any chance?
إذن ليس لدي أي فرصة؟
♫Love flames rise wild in the night♫
♫ لهيب الحب يتصاعد في الليل ♫
♫Reaching their arms out to the sky♫
تصل أذرعهم إلى السماء
You don't want to be the same kind of person.
أنت لا تريد أن تكون من نفس النوع من الأشخاص.
♫Tonight it's still pitch black♫
♫ الليلة لا يزال اللون الأسود قاتمًا ♫
I won't force you.
لن اجبرك.
Then you're my enemy.
إذن أنت عدوي.
♫I'm like a moth♫
♫ أنا مثل العثة ♫
♫Dancing with the fire♫
الرقص بالنار ♫
I don't want to hear
لا اريد ان اسمع
any more nonsense.
أي مزيد من الهراء.
♫The fire is bright and only ashes remain♫
النار مشرقة ولا يبقى منها إلا الرماد ♫
♫You destroyed everything♫
لقد دمرت كل شيء ♫
♫Traces of good memories♫
آثار الذكريات الطيبة ♫
♫All past is fading rapidly♫
كل الماضي يتلاشى بسرعة
♫As empty as anything♫
فارغة كأي شيء ♫
♫Dancing with the fire♫
الرقص بالنار ♫
♫The fire is bright and only ashes remain♫
النار مشرقة ولا يبقى منها إلا الرماد ♫
♫Can't turn away♫
♫ لا تستطيع الابتعاد
♫Slow down my rhythms♫
♫ إبطاء إيقاعاتي ♫
♫The fire is bright♫
النار مشرقة ♫
♫You and I are worn out together♫
♫ أنت وأنا مرهقون معًا ♫
♫The deeper the love is♫
كلما كان الحب أعمق ♫
♫The more we get hurt♫
كلما تأذينا أكثر
Why didn't you call me?
لماذا لم تتصل بي
Aren't we partners?
ألسنا شركاء؟
I didn't call you.
لم أتصل بك.
Aren't you still here?
الا مازلت هنا؟
Do you have a clip
هل لديك مقطع
or a pin?
أو دبوس؟
I have nothing on me.
ليس لدي أي شيء علي.
I don't even know where the box is.
أنا لا أعرف حتى أين يوجد الصندوق.
Stop talking.
توقف عن الكلام.
Do you need a tool to pick the lock?
هل تحتاج إلى أداة لفتح القفل؟
It's not difficult to pick.
ليس من الصعب الاختيار.
But I don't have a pry.
لكن ليس لدي نقب.
Stop looking for it.
توقف عن البحث عنها.
It's all foam plastic.
كلها من البلاستيك الرغوي.
What should we do now?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل الآن؟
Will this work?
هل سيعمل هذا؟
Let's try.
لنجرب.
Let me do it.
دعني افعلها.
You have to pick the lock later.
عليك أن تختار القفل لاحقًا.
It's okay.
حسنا.
Are you sure this will work?
هل أنت متأكد من أن هذا سيعمل؟
Straighten these nails
افرد هذه الأظافر
and twist them together.
ولفهم معًا.
Theoretically, it's feasible.
من الناحية النظرية ، هذا ممكن.
If we can get out this time,
إذا تمكنا من الخروج هذه المرة ،
you can come back to the vintage store anytime you want.
يمكنك العودة إلى المتجر القديم في أي وقت تريده.
Forget it if you didn't hear me.
انسى الأمر إذا لم تسمعني.
Fine.
بخير.
Here.
هنا.
It's done.
تم التنفيذ.
Let me do it.
دعني افعلها.
You have to pick the lock later.
عليك أن تختار القفل لاحقًا.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
♫I got a reason to live♫
♫ لدي سبب للعيش ♫
♫I got a fire inside♫
♫ اشتعلت النيران بالداخل ♫
♫I got something to fight for♫
♫ لدي شيء أقاتل من أجله
♫Nothing can hold me down♫
♫ لا شيء يمكن أن يثقل كاهلي ♫
♫I got a fire inside♫
♫ اشتعلت النيران بالداخل ♫
♫I got something to fight for♫
♫ لدي شيء أقاتل من أجله
♫Nothing can hold me down♫
♫ لا شيء يمكن أن يثقل كاهلي ♫
♫I got a reason to live♫
♫ لدي سبب للعيش ♫
♫I got something to fight for♫
♫ لدي شيء أقاتل من أجله
♫Nothing can hold me down♫
♫ لا شيء يمكن أن يثقل كاهلي ♫
♫I got a reason to live♫
♫ لدي سبب للعيش ♫
♫I got something to fight for♫
♫ لدي شيء أقاتل من أجله
♫I got a reason to love♫
♫ لدي سبب للحب ♫
Aren't you afraid they'll kill me?
ألا تخشى أن يقتلوني؟
Because I'm sure
لأنني متأكد
I can save you.
أستطيع أن أنقذك.
What if...
ماذا إذا...
What if?
ماذا إذا؟
Then you'll have to pray.
ثم عليك أن تصلي.
[Clinical Education Hospital at Zhaonuan Vocational Education Center]
[مستشفى التعليم السريري في مركز التعليم المهني Zhaonuan]
[Clinical Teaching Hospital of Zhaonuan Nursing School]
[مستشفى التدريس السريري في مدرسة التمريض Zhaonuan]
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
What happened to you?
ماذا حدث لك؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Didn't you take up the project?
ألم تأخذ المشروع؟
I was scared to death, you know?
كنت خائفة حتى الموت ، هل تعلم؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Why are you laughing?
لماذا تضحك؟
Do you know how worried I was?
هل تعلم كم كنت قلقة؟
I know now.
أعلم الآن.
Does it hurt?
هل تؤلم؟
It's okay.
حسنا.
It looks serious.
تبدو جادة.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Seeing you care so much about me,
برؤيتك تهتم بي كثيرا ،
I couldn't be happier.
لا يمكنني أن أكون أكثر سعادة.
Are you crazy?
هل أنت مجنون؟
Are you stupid?
هل انت غبي؟
Yes.
نعم.
I miss you so much that I'm stupid.
أفتقدك كثيرًا لدرجة أنني غبي.
You're crazy. It's not the time to be like this.
انت مجنون.  إنه ليس الوقت المناسب لتكون هكذا.
All right, stop crying.
حسنًا ، توقف عن البكاء.
I'm really tired today.
أنا متعب حقًا اليوم.
Can you hug me?
هل يمكنك معانقي؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I shouldn't have made you worry about me.
ما كان يجب أن أجعلك تقلق علي.
I won't do it again.
لن أفعل ذلك مرة أخرى.
If you do it again,
إذا قمت بذلك مرة أخرى ،
I won't forgive you.
لن أسامحك.
I promise it won't happen again.
أعدك أن ذلك لن يحدث مرة أخرى.
Are you really okay?
هل انت حقا بخير
Do you need a full body check?
هل تحتاج إلى فحص كامل للجسم؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
No.
لا.
You still need to have a check.
ما زلت بحاجة إلى التحقق.
I'll go find the doctor.
سأذهب لأجد الطبيب.
I'm really fine.
أنا بخير حقا.
You are my best doctor.
أنت أفضل طبيبي.
Hello,
مرحبًا،
the subscriber you dialed is busy now.
المشترك الذي طلبته مشغول الآن.
Please try again later.
الرجاء معاودة المحاولة في وقت لاحق.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
The subscriber you dialed is busy now.
المشترك الذي طلبته مشغول الآن.
Please try again later.
الرجاء معاودة المحاولة في وقت لاحق.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Chufeng.
تشوفينج.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
You don't even want to call me master?
أنت لا تريد حتى أن تناديني سيد؟
Do you know
هل تعرف
why I called you?
لماذا اتصلت بك
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
You know.
أنت تعرف.
You know me better than anyone.
أنت تعرفني أفضل من أي شخص آخر.
You are the most similar person
أنت أكثر شخص مشابه
to me in this world.
لي في هذا العالم.
You know why
تعرف لماذا
I called you.
اتصلت بك.
You know what I want.
أنت تعرف ماذا أريد.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Stop calling Sui Yi.
توقف عن استدعاء Sui Yi.
You can't find her.
لا يمكنك العثور عليها.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
I want her to die.
اريدها ان تموت
OK?
نعم؟
No.
لا.
What?
لما؟
You're heartbroken?
أنت حزين؟
Your family died because of you.
عائلتك ماتت بسببك.
Do you still care about one more death?
هل مازلت تهتم بموت آخر؟
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
Now you care about me.
الآن أنت تهتم بي.
You want to know where I am.
تريد أن تعرف مكاني.
I'm the one you want to revenge.
أنا من تريد الانتقام.
She's innocent.
إنها بريئة.
No one is innocent.
لا أحد بريء.
People who are with you
الناس الذين معك
will definitely be involved.
بالتأكيد سوف تشارك.
I beg you.
أرجوك.
What?
لما؟
You beg me?
تتوسل لي؟
Okay.
تمام.
Great.
عظيم.
He Chufeng.
انه Chufeng.
Let me see
لنرى
how you will beg me in person.
كيف ستتوسل لي شخصيًا.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
[Sui Yi sent a location]
[أرسلت سوي يي موقعًا]
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Where are you now?
أين أنت الآن؟
My phone is with you.
هاتفي معك.
I have something to do.
لدي شي لأقوم به.
I'll call you later.
سوف اتصل بك لاحقا.
You're here.
أنت هنا.
Where is Sui Yi?
أين سوي يي؟
Where is she?
أين هي؟
Is this how beg me?
هل هذا كيف تتوسل لي؟
What do you want to do?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل؟
Don't you know
لا تعرف
what I want to do?
ماذا اريد ان افعل
I told you
أخبرتك
you are the person I trust the most.
أنت أكثر شخص أثق به.
I don't care about the money.
لا يهمني المال.
I just want to give a lesson to those who laughed at me,
أريد فقط أن أعطي درسًا لأولئك الذين سخروا مني ،
mocked me
سخر مني
and looked down on me.
ونظرت إليّ بازدراء.
You know it.
أنت تعرفها.
But what did you do?
لكن ماذا فعلت؟
You ruined me.
لقد خربتني.
Everyone around you
كل من حولك
died because of you.
مات بسببك.
I'm the one
أنا الأول
who gave you hope.
من أعطاك الأمل.
Are you going to kill me?
هل ستقتلني؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
You're sorry.
أنت آسف.
What's the use of apologizing?
ما فائدة الاعتذار؟
You sent me in.
لقد أرسلتني.
My hands
يداي
are crippled.
مشلولون.
I can't pick locks anymore.
لا يمكنني اختيار الأقفال بعد الآن.
But you...
لكنك...
You have a great life every day.
لديك حياة رائعة كل يوم.
Why?
لماذا؟
Yes.
نعم.
You should be sorry to me.
يجب أن تكون آسف لي.
If it weren't for you,
إذا لم تكن لك ،
my life will be
ستكون حياتي
greater than yours.
أعظم منك.
All your discontent
كل ما تبذلونه من استياء
is because of me.
هو بسببي.
Come at me if you want to do anything.
تعال إلي إذا كنت تريد أن تفعل أي شيء.
Come at me, okay?
تعال إلي ، حسنًا؟
If you have any complaints,
إذا كانت لديك أية شكاوى ،
I beg you,
أرجوك،
address them to me.
خاطبهم لي.
Hit me. Beat me.
ضربني.  اضربني.
I can do anything you want.
أستطيع أن أفعل أي شيء تريده.
But I forbid you to hurt anyone else again.
لكني أمنعك من إيذاء أي شخص آخر مرة أخرى.
I understand now.
أنا أفهم الآن.
He Chufeng.
انه Chufeng.
You still think I'm the only one
ما زلت تعتقد أنني الوحيد
who did wrong, right?
من فعل الخطأ صحيح؟
I know.
أنا أعرف.
You think
أتظن
you are a noble
انت نبيل
and dedicated person
وشخص مخصص
and you are proud of that.
وأنت فخور بذلك.
As for me,
بالنسبة لي،
a despicable
حقير
and shameless person.
وشخص وقح.
But don't forget
لكن لا تنسى
I gave you everything.
أعطيتك كل شيء.
I also taught you your skills.
كما علمتك مهاراتك.
If I hadn't
إذا لم أفعل
found you in the garage,
وجدتك في المرآب ،
you would still be fixing broken cars there.
كنت لا تزال تصلح السيارات المعطلة هناك.
If I knew
لو كنت اعلم
you would become like this,
ستصبح هكذا ،
I wouldn't have asked you to teach me.
لم أكن لأطلب منك أن تعلمني.
If I had known,
لو كنت أعلم،
I would rather live in darkness from the beginning.
أفضل العيش في الظلام من البداية.
You know what I care about.
أنت تعرف ما يهمني.
I thought...
اعتقدت...
I thought you really let it go.
اعتقدت أنك حقا تركتها تذهب.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
It's all because of me.
كل هذا بسببي.
I shouldn't have gone to you.
ما كان يجب أن أذهب إليك.
I shouldn't have followed you.
لا يجب أن أتبعك.
I brought you so much pain.
جلبت لك الكثير من الألم.
It was my choice
كان خياري
that kept torturing you.
الذي ظل يعذبك.
Let all the pain
دع كل الألم
that I have caused you
الذي سببته لك
from the beginning end with me.
من البداية تنتهي معي.
Just let yourself go.
فقط دع نفسك تذهب.
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
As long as you release Sui Yi,
طالما أطلقت سراح Sui Yi ،
and let me take her back,
واسمحوا لي أن أعيدها ،
I can return everything
يمكنني إعادة كل شيء
you taught me,
أنت علمتني،
including my life.
بما في ذلك حياتي.
♫You hide You hide♫
تخفي أنت تخفي ♫
♫So she said...♫
♫ هكذا قالت ... ♫
♫In spite...I've tried♫
♫ على الرغم من ... لقد حاولت ♫
♫To give a home of my own♫
لإعطاء منزل خاص بي ♫
♫Never could have seen♫
♫ لم يسبق له مثيل ♫
♫Never could have dreamed♫
♫ ما كان يمكن أن أحلم
♫Of it all coming together♫
من كل ذلك معا ♫
It's enough for you to suffer alone.
يكفي أن تعاني وحدك.
♫You brought me a warm home♫
♫ أحضرت لي منزلًا دافئًا ♫
Why would you make another person
لماذا تجعل شخصًا آخر
suffer like you?
تعاني مثلك
I want him to be like me.
اريده ان يكون مثلي
♫You wait I fade♫
♫ انتظري اتلاشى ♫
You're the one who did wrong.
أنت الشخص الذي أخطأ.
Whatever the reason is,
مهما كان السبب ،
♫So she said...♫
♫ هكذا قالت ... ♫
You shouldn't have picked that lock,
لا يجب أن تختار هذا القفل ،
let alone blame
ناهيك عن اللوم
♫I fake, afraid♫
♫ أنا مزيف ، خائف ♫
Chufeng for this.
Chufeng لهذا.
Chufeng's life
حياة Chufeng
♫Know that I'm alone♫
♫ أعلم أنني وحدي ♫
is something you can't control.
شيء لا يمكنك السيطرة عليه.
♫Never could have seen♫
♫ لم يسبق له مثيل
♫Never could have dreamed♫
♫ لم أكن لأحلم أبدًا
No one can.
لا احد يستطيع.
♫Of it all coming together♫
من كل ذلك معا ♫
♫You brought me a warm home♫
♫ أحضرت لي منزلًا دافئًا ♫
Let's see if He Chufeng
دعونا نرى ما إذا كان هو Chufeng
will pick this lock.
سيختار هذا القفل.
♫Make a complete family with me♫
♫ اصنع عائلة كاملة معي
Go to the intersection of Chengjia Road and Minghe Road.
اذهب إلى تقاطع طريق Chengjia وطريق Minghe.
There's an abandoned factory.
هناك مصنع مهجور.
There's a safe inside.
هناك خزنة بالداخل.
Take it out and send it to the forest.
أخرجه وأرسله إلى الغابة.
Someone will pick you up.
شخص ما سوف يقلك.
♫I think of them tonight♫
♫ أفكر فيهم الليلة ♫
Lock is
القفل
nothing good or bad.
لا شيء جيد أو سيء.
It's not a bad thing to pick locks.
اختيار الأقفال ليس بالأمر السيئ.
But it depends on our hearts
لكن الأمر يعتمد على قلوبنا
to save or harm people.
لإنقاذ الناس أو إيذائهم.
♫And that night Charlie started crying♫
♫ وفي تلك الليلة بدأ تشارلي في البكاء ♫
I want to be like you,
اريد ان اكون مثلك،
♫And fleed to faraway places♫
وهربوا إلى أماكن بعيدة ♫
a locksmith who can save people.
صانع الأقفال الذي يمكن أن ينقذ الناس.
♫So how did they go♫
♫ فكيف ذهبوا ♫
♫Are they still deep in the mud♫
هل هم مازالوا عميقاً في الوحل
♫There were too many tears that night♫
"كان هناك الكثير من الدموع في تلك الليلة"
♫And we all know the reason♫
♫ وكلنا نعرف السبب ♫
♫Halfway through the night♫
في منتصف الليل ♫
♫The person I'm expecting hasn't shown up♫
♫ الشخص الذي أتوقعه لم يظهر
Do you think it's okay to give it back to me?
هل تعتقد أنه من المقبول إعادتها إلي؟
Are you able to give it all back?
هل أنت قادر على إعادتها كلها؟
♫Lonely like walking dead♫
♫ وحيدا مثل المشي ميتا ♫
He Chufeng.
انه Chufeng.
What you owe me
ماذا تدين لي
can never be repaid.
لا يمكن سداده أبدًا.
♫Wanted to walk away but I'm still waiting♫
♫ أردت أن أمشي بعيدًا لكنني ما زلت أنتظر
Take a look.
إلق نظرة.
The latest model.
أحدث طراز.
It's very popular in North America these two years.
إنها تحظى بشعبية كبيرة في أمريكا الشمالية خلال هذين العامين.
This is its first appearance in China.
هذا هو أول ظهور لها في الصين.
It contains a special substance.
يحتوي على مادة خاصة.
One can make people lose their mind.
يمكن للمرء أن يجعل الناس يفقدون عقولهم.
♫I want to leave everything behind♫
♫ أريد أن أترك كل شيء ورائي
It's also illegal to sell this.
كما أنه من غير القانوني بيع هذا.
♫Leave as if I don't care about anything♫
♫ ارحل كأنني لا أهتم بأي شيء ♫
♫Stay away from here♫
ابتعد عن هنا ♫
I'll take care of this myself.
سأعتني بهذا بنفسي.
Let what started with me
دع ما بدأ معي
end with me.
تنتهي معي.
Sui Yi.
سوي يي.
No matter where you are,
لا يهم أين أنت،
I will find you.
سوف أجدك.
You must wait for me.
يجب أن تنتظرني.
So,
وبالتالي،
what kind of life do you want?
اي نوع من الحياة تريد
I want a life in which I can
أريد حياة أستطيع فيها
follow my inner voice  and be myself
اتبع صوتي الداخلي وكن على طبيعتي
without thinking too much.
دون تفكير كثيرا.
I want a life in which
اريد حياة فيها
I can live in an upright manner
أستطيع أن أعيش في وضع مستقيم
without caring what others think.
دون الاهتمام بما يعتقده الآخرون.
[Monster Notebook]
[مفكرة الوحش]
[To be continued]
[يتبع]